One, two! One, two, three!
Froggie went a-courtin'
and he did ride
Well, Froggie went a-courtin'
Somethin' Bender is great
Froggie went a-courtin'
and Bender is great
Uh-huh
Oh, my God!
They dug up a bag of Olestra chips
from my time.
There must be layers and layers
of old stuff down there.
Oh!
What's that?
One of those Led Zeppelins
I've heard so much about?
No, it's an old Volkswagen van.
Hey, mister, mind if I take this old van?
Sure. You want to dump the corpses
out of theres, it's yourses.
Yeah, yeah. I've gotten used cars before.
What's that?
One of those Jefferson Starships
I've heard so much about?
It's called a van. And in light of
the fact that it's not a-rockin',
I invite you to come a-knockin'.
Wow! Neat!
It's a triumph
of free-spirited German engineering.
Hey! The speedometer only goes up to 80.
This thing can't go faster
than 80,000 miles an hour?
No, it can't. But it's got
a driver's side floor
and an eight-track player
with genuine mono sound.
Where's the device that lets you speed
or slow the passage of time?
Under the seat.
Why won't it start?
It just needs some gas.
Wrong again, idiot. There is no gas.
Petroleum reserves ran dry in 2038.
Gas was an environmental disaster anyway.
Now we use alternative fuels.
- Like what?
- Whale oil.
Bender, lift it up to the can opener.
Oh, no! I'm not going near it.
Last time, that magnetic psycho
nearly cut my head off.
Oh, right. Plus, the magnet
screws up your inhibition unit
and makes you sing folk songs.
What? Who said anything about me
secretly wanting to be a folk singer?
How ridiculous!
Bender, if you don't open that can
right now, your fear will own you.
And nothing that can opener could ever do
would be worse than that.
Okay. Okay. I can do this.
It's time to take life by the cans.
- Come on.
- You can do it.
Go on, you dummy.
Jimmy crack corn
and I don't care
Jimmy crack corn and I don't care
Oh, no!
I don't care 'cause the master's gone away
It's toe-tappingly tragic.
Doc, I can't move my arms and legs.
What's wrong with me?
This is the worst part of the job.
- What is it? Good news?
- Bender, your hydraulics are shot.
You'll never move again.
- You mean...
- I'm sorry.
You'll have to get a new one.
Poor Bender.
Well, let's drag him to the curb.
Wait a minute. Bender is my best friend.
We can't just dump him in the gutter
like Grandma's ashes.
Oh! My life is over.
I'll never know happiness again.
Hello there.
Look, Bender. It's Patch Cord Adams.
He heals with the power of laughter.
Come on. Take it.
What's the matter? Can't move your arms?
Obviously not,
or I'd be strangling you right now.
Hey, here's a giggle.
Did you hear why they're using
Windows 3000 as a prison guard?
- No. Why?
- 'Cause it always locks up.
For the love of God,
somebody kick his ass!
Well, so long. Get well soon.
Whoa. Well. So long anyway.
Oh, I'm doomed!
Everybody leave me alone.
I don't wanna be seen this way.
Aw, you look so sad.
You want me to send
Patch Cord Adams back in?
Hey, the blues.
The tragic sound
of other people's suffering.
That's kind of a pick-me-up.
- Wow, that was great!
- Hey, thanks. You a fan?
I don't know. Let me see.
Oh, my God, you're Beck!
I'd get up to shake your hand
and steal your wallet,
but my crappy body crapped out on me.
Don't take it so hard.
I used to miss my body, too,
but then I fished this mannequin out
of the 92-Cent Store Dumpster.
Wow! We've sure got a lot in common, Beck.
I always dreamed of being
a musician-poet who transcends genres,
even as he reinvents them, just like you.
So do it, robot.
It's easier than it looks.
Yeah, thanks, but it's hopeless.
I'll never be a musician now.
Or maybe you'll be
the best musician ever.
What's this for?
Try and scrape it across your chest,
like a knife on burnt toast.
Come on. Move those arms.
Use the power of mental thinking.
Make it dynamic.
Yeah! All right.
Congratulations, my friend.
Why? 'Cause I can make annoying noises?
Exactly. I use those
all the time in my music.
Bender, I want you to become
my new washboard player.
All right!
Go Bender! Go Bender! Go Bender!
Well, that's my good friend Beck.
I'm off to rock a series
of mid-level venues.
Kudos, Bender.
You got mangled, and now you're a singer.
Both our dreams came true.
Hey, I have an idea.
Who wants to cram in my van
and follow Bender on tour
and live there in the van?
I don't know, Fry. I think I'm too poor
to follow a band around in a van.
Come on. Move it.
We gotta get to the concert
and make the audience
wait for it to start.
Bad news, friends.
My shell ran.
Zoidberg, you idiot!
My outfit... It's... It's...
- Kind of cool.
- Yeah. I like it.
- Me, too, now that I'm used to it.
- Then it was all on purpose.
You're lucky to have Zoidberg as a friend.
But cross me,
and I'll turn on you like that.
There's a destination a little up the road
From the habitations and the towns we know
A place we saw the lights turn low
The jigsaw jazz and the get-fresh flow
Pulling out jives and jamboree handouts
Two turntables and a microphone
Bottles and cans
just clap your hands
Just clap your hands
Where it's at
Got a washboard stomach and a microphone
That was a washboard brain
Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
One bowl of Jell-O knuckles, please.
That'll be three "pic-a-tures"
of George Washington.
Oh, no! My beautiful money!
- It got ruined in the wash.
- Mine, too. Even my change.
Get lost, you moneyless hippies!
You heard him, freaks.
We don't like your type around here.
These are the types we like.
Bender, that was the best
40-minute washboard solo I've ever heard.
The parts when I was awake
blew my mind.
Whoa. Check out all those broken robots.
Howdy, fellas!
Oh, I don't believe my broken eyes!
It's Bender, the washboard player!
Hey, man, we caught your concert
from here.
You rock!
Oh, oh, Bender, sign my chest!
It's in that bin behind me.
Yo, brother! Thanks for showin'
that broken robots are still useful.
Aw, hang in there, folks.
I bet before you know it,
you guys'll be...
That is so wrong!
You can't just melt down broken robots.
Not right when they're kissing my ass.
Whoa, dawg. Just cold chill.
You know, when I'm upset,
I write a song about it.
Like, when I wrote "Devil's Haircut,"
I was feeling really...
- What's that song about?
- Hey, yeah.
I could write a song. With real words.
Not phony ones, like "odelay."
"Odelay" is a word.
Just look it up in the Becktionary.
Ooh.
I'm workin' on my song.
Hand me the Becktionary.
No, no, the rhyming Becktionary.
I wish I could help
raise awareness about broken robots.
But what can I do?
I only weigh eight pounds.
Wait a minute.
You know lots of rock stars.
And most of them like to look
like they care about things.
We can all get together for
a big benefit concert in San Francisco.
And we can call it "Bend-Aid"
after me, Bender.
And you can sing that song you're writing.
And I'll let you sing backup.
But remember who the star is.
Me, Bender.
All right. "Hands in the air"
rhymes with "just don't care."
And finished!
Ugh! Smells like something
died in the wall.
Surprise!
Mind if we crash here tonight?
The colors in the van
are keeping us awake.
All right, but hands off the minibar.
Wow! I forgot about TV.
Living free on the road,
you realize how much better
life is without it.
Well, let's see what's on.
Tuesday, Golden Gate Park...
The monsters of vaguely
folkish alterna-rock
will strum your brains out
at Bend-Aid!
Featuring Beck, Wailing Fungus
and special guest Bender!
A portion of the proceeds
might go to help broken robots.
- Yeah!
- Hooray! Great.
- Bender, you're famous!
- Yeah.
This coming together of superstars
really means a lot to you,
doesn't it, Bender?
Uh-huh.
Helping my defective brothers
is the first thing I've ever cared about,
even the slightest bit.
You know, when I first got broken,
I thought my life was over,
but look at me now.
I got fame, money, groupies,
and it's all thanks to
being completely immobilized.
That's why I'll be proud
to go up on stage tomorrow and say,
"Look at me, world! I am a broken robot!"
Bender, you can move. You're cured.
Oh, crap! It's a miracle!
I can move again.
My music career is over.
Bender, I don't claim
to understand "the biz,"
but wouldn't being able to move
help your music career?
No! Don't you see?
I was a hero to broken robots
'cause I was one of them.
But how can I sing about
being damaged if I'm not?
That's like Christina Aguilera
singin' in Spanish.
Wait! That's it! I'll fake it.
You better not do that at the concert.
I can't stop. When I eat too much dirt,
I get stuff in my throat.
Ugh! You are so disgusting. I...
They're beautiful!
Ew. You're touching them.
I've never seen pearls like this.
Dr. Zoidberg, you're amazing!
I am? At last, recognition!
Gentle hippies,
put your filthy hands together
for the folk stylings
of Cylon and Garfunkel!
Here's a song that was beautiful
when performed by my ancestor, Art.
Are you goin'
to Scarborough Fair
Parsley, sage, rosemary and thyme
Remember me
To one who lives there
She once was
A true love of mine
- We're home.
- Well, let's earn some bread.
Brothers and sisters, get your love beads.
Can't journey to the center of your mind
without love beads.
Wow, look at the colors!
These'll go great with my soul.
Glad you like them. I've been making
fine jewelry for years, apparently.
- I'll take three.
- Give me one, man.
I'll trade you a bad poem.
And now, stand up and turn on
your hidden tape recorders
for Beck!
With special guest,
Bender, the Broken Robot!
- Bender rules!
- Groove on, man!
Rock it, Bender!
Can't you hear
those cavalry drums
Hijacking your equilibrium
-Oh, yeah
-Midnight snacks
In the mausoleum
Thank you. That song doesn't
usually last three hours,
but we got into a serious thing,
and then I forgot how it ended.
Anyway, one last item
of business before we go.
Bender, to start your foundation
for broken robots,
here's a big cardboard check for $14,000.
It's been an emotional day for me.
I don't know what to say.
Then maybe you should sing it.
Lay it down, boys.
Ladies, gentlemen,
smoking heaps of machinery...
This is a song called "My Broken Friend."
People say
my broken friend is useless
But I say his mind is free
There's lots of things
my mangled robot friend could be
Kick it.
He could make a good hat rack
He only has to stand there
-Or a cheap doorstop
-He doesn't need to move
-Or a great big giant thermos
-Giant thermos
-With a twist-off top
-That would be good for soup
He could be a storage closet
For outdated pants
I like 'em tight
My broken friend could do it all
Just give him a chance
That robot has a tragic secret
That I'd like to share
For real?
My broken friend is closer to me
Than an ass to a chair
Mmm.
That robot's name I never told you
Who's that?
You could not foresee
Come on. Give it up.
I'll say it loud and sing it proud
His name is you and me
-Don't melt me down into a crowbar
-That suffers alone
-Just 'cause I can't move my arms and legs
-Arms and legs
Or toss me into a trash can
Bender, what are you doing?
Just 'cause I can't cook you ham and eggs
What are you doing?
Don't crush me into an anchor
Yo, what's the dillio?
Just 'cause I can't jump
and dance and sing
But... No. But, Bender...
I'm telling you my broken friend
Put your hands in the air
like you just don't care
No...
I'm telling you my broken friend
Can do most
Cut it.
Anything
- Yeah!
- Cut it!
Curse my natural showmanship!
You big, fat fraud!
You're not really broken!
But you will be in a minute!
Bum-rush the stage!
Get him!
Whoa!
Oh, harsh! I didn't get my beads.
You, minion, lift up my arm.
After him!
Well, everyone, prepare to get
your guts kicked out by folk singers.
What is this? The Year of the Jerk?
Hurry! The Golden Gate Bridge.
Put the metal to the pedal
to the other metal.
Oh, no! I forgot this is a hoverbridge.
And I forgot this isn't a hover car!
Is any of that a problem?
Not if you've lived a life without regret.
I'll save me!
Quick, grab his foot cuffs!
Bummer.
Someone fat get in my way!
I'm broken again.
- I can't move any part of me.
- Good.
I'm really sorry I lied, Beck.
All I ever wanted
was to make music with you.
I never meant to hurt anyone,
or help anyone.
Bender, that's some played-out,
new jack horse crap.
But I know you don't mean it,
so apology accepted.
So, I can keep the check?
Over my dead career!
Well, it was worth a shot.
Come on, Bender! If you're done
scamming Beck, we're heading home.
All right, all right.
Let me just do one thing
to cheer myself up.
Right!
Fry crack corn and I don't care
Leela crack corn
I still don't care
Bender crack corn and he is great
Take that, you stupid corn